## Paul Marrable

# Web Developer

e: paul.marrable@plinx-tech.co.uk w: www.paulmarrable.co.uk m: 07824 366376

#### Personal Profile

I am currently a full stack developer for the New Media department at Listers in Stratford. I also run an independent video game studio called Flump Studios.

I have been developing software and games for over 25 years and I have maintained a strong passion for software development, with the art of clean coding being of particular interest. Over the years I have gained experience developing with C#, C++, Javascript, Typescript, Python, VB, Lua, Unity 3D, HTML, CSS, SASS, AngularJS, ReactJS, ASP.Net, SQL and various other languages and frameworks.

As a web developer, my current preferred stack is C# .Net Core 2+ , Entity FW core and ReactJS with Redux.

## Work Experience

#### Full stack web developer

Jan 2018 - Present

API, Web app and website design and development. Currently leading the development of a web API and SPA data store project using .NET Core 2+, React with redux, and MSsql with Entity FW core.

#### Full stack web developer

Apr 2016 - Jan 2018

Web app, API, website design and development. Working primarily with C# .NET and .NET Core, React, AngularJs, Umbraco and MSsql with Entity FW Core and ADO.

#### Video Game Developer

Jan 2011 - present

Design and developerment of independent video games, both solo and part of a small team. For my more recent projects I have been using Unity3D with C#, moving over from C# with XNA/Monogame to aid development speed. For many years Flump Studios was my full time job, until my first son was born and decided I needed something more stable.

### Key Skills

C#
.NET Core
React JS
Typescript
HTML/CSS/JS
SQL/Entity Framework
TDD
GIT
Agile

#### Education

Uxbridge College 09/1997 - 07/2000 GNVQ in IT BTEC National Diploma in Computer studies